真相是什么
What is the truth?
-你杀人吗  -不
- Do you kill people? - No.
以后别骗我了
No more lies, please.
再也没有谎言
No more lies.
我的美国朋友搜集到了一些聊天记录
My American friend picked up some chatter.
雕塑百科全书
罗丹
思考者是一尊由奥古斯特·罗丹创作的青铜雕塑 通常置于石座之上
雕塑描绘了一位坐在岩石上的裸体男性英雄形象 好似在沉思 常被用作象征哲学的形象
罗丹的价格已达成一致
Rodin price point agreed.
豺狼已在路上
Jackal en route.
有人买凶要杀你
A contract's been taken out on your life.
-是谁买凶  -我们不知道 先生
- Who's taken out this contract? - We don't have that information, sir.
诺曼肯定知道我们要来
Norman definitely knew we were coming.
诺曼·斯托克 到底是何许人
Who exactly is this Norman Stoke?
狙击手带走了他用来杀死费斯特的武器
The sniper took the weapon he used to kill Fest with him,
就像这样
and this is how he did it.
这都多亏了诺曼·斯托克
All thanks to Norman Stoke.
诺曼 我要个地址
Norman.I need an address.
我问问我的人
I'll talk to my man.
我要让你亲眼见证
I want you to see this.
我问你答
Tell me everything I need to know.
妈
Mum!
豺狼现在在哪
The Jackal, where is he now?
应该在塔林
He should be in Tallinn.
你去找他 跟着他
You need to find him and stay with him.
你好
Hello.
塔林  爱沙尼亚
雇主已经给了你两千万美元
You've taken twenty million dollars from people
他们希望付出的每一分钱都能带来回报
who are used to getting what they paid for.
并且 他们给你钱 不是让你在慕尼黑私自行动
And they didn't pay you to go rogue in Munich.
如果我没有兑现承诺
If I don't deliver,
如果你没有兑现承诺
if you don't deliver,
他们会采取极端手段
they will take extreme measures.
你肯定不会想和他们为敌
You do not want to make enemies of these people.
他们的强大超乎你想象
They're more powerful than you know.
你不相信我的话
If you don't believe me...
就去问问诺曼·斯托克
...just ask Norman Stoke.
我比谁都希望你能成功
Nobody wants you to succeed more than me.
我非常欣赏你的能力
I'm a huge admirer of your work.
豺狼的日子
第一季 第五集
事成前 我会一直待在塔林
I'll be staying in Tallinn until delivery, so...
有需要可以随时联系我
If you need anything you can call me.
我的手机安保很强
My phone's secure.
缺保姆行吗
A babysitter
什么都行
Anything.
思考者还是臭皮匠
你没事吧
You alright?
我很好
Great.
比安卡 当我们...
Look, Bianca. When we...
他想杀我女儿
He tried to kill my daughter.
有道理
Fair point.
出去
Outside.
快点出去
Go on, off you fuck.
谁都不许进来 明白吗
No-one comes in. Understood?
诺曼在哪
Where's Norman?
操你妈
Fuck you.
你别不信
Trust me when I say,
我一定会找到诺曼 然后亲手干掉他
I will find Norman and I will kill him myself.
她可没开玩笑
She ain't fucking about.
我们不是警察 我们不需要逮捕令
We're not police. We don't need arrest warrants.
她一旦找到他 就会杀了他
She finds him, she's gonna kill him.
告诉我们有用信息
Tell us what we need to know...
这样一来 第一
...and one,
我们不杀诺曼
we don't kill Norman.
第二 你不会被判终身监禁
Two, instead of you going to prison for life,
而是你们兄弟俩一起 多少来着 最多判五年
the two of you do... ...what, five years max.
优美 舒适的监狱 你好好想想 就五年 拉里
Nice, comfy prison. You'll do five standing on your head, Larry.
第三
And three...
你可以回家安葬艾莉森 艾玛 悼念她们
You get to go home to bury Alison, Emma, and say your goodbyes.
所以 你愿意开口吗
So, you gonna to speak to me?
不说
No?
操你妈
Fuck you.
新邮件
关闭
打开
委托你帮我做个东西 非常特别
报酬也很丰厚 你应该会感兴趣
你那边安全吗
你那边安全吗？
打这个号码：+36 55 723 913
发送
附加文件
上次的表现真是精彩
'Congratulations on your last performance.'
谢谢 那是因为器械恰到好处才得以成功的
Thank you. It was only made possible by a very fine instrument.
大师出品
Made by a maestro.
是啊 最棒的 所以我才做回头客
'Yeah, the best. That's why I keep coming back.'
你这次需要什么
'What do you need this time?'
说这事前
Er, before I get to that, um...
我想先问你个问题 诺曼
I've got a question for you, Norman.
说
'Shoot.'
你最近怎么了
What's been going on with you?
-你指什么  -我是说
- What'd you mean? - 'I mean...'
你最近有没有遇到什么
Have you experienced anything unusual...
不寻常的事
'..recently?'
也算是不寻常吧
You could say 'unusual', yeah.
-你怎么知道的  -具体是什么
- 'How did you know?' - What exactly?
我得先知道才能继续我们的话题
I need to know before we can... go any further.
我那会在出差
'I was on a business trip.'
在国外 出现了一些访客
Abroad. Some visitors showed up.
他们没被邀请也没带花
They weren't invited and they weren't bringing flowers.
他们是谁
'Who were they?'
我没跟他们闲聊
I didn't stop to chat.
就这么说吧 我给了他们一个小小的贝尔法斯特式欢迎
'Let's just say I gave 'em a wee Belfast welcome,
然后我就走了
then I got out of there.'
我把他们处理掉了
'I dealt with them.'
好吧 那你现在百分百安全吗
Right, and you're 100% secure now?
百分百
'One hundred percent.'
你知道我不喜欢冒险
You know I don't like risks.
你知道我也不喜欢
'You know I don't either.'
距离目标有75米
Distance to the target is 75 metres.
你可不喜欢这么近的
'Not like you to get that snug.'
确实 可惜我没得选
'Yeah. Unfortunately, it's my only option.'
有什么障碍
What are the obstacles?
金属探测器 还有超敏扫描仪
A metal detector and an ultra-sensitive scanner
但我有办法搞定
but I've got an idea for that.
你什么时候需要
When you need it?
要在五天内做好
'Well, the job's in five days.'
有点困难
There's a problem.
-开个价吧 老哥  -不
- Name your price, old man. - 'Nah.'
不是钱的事 还记得我刚说的访客吗
It's not about the money. The visitors I mentioned?
我胳膊被擦伤了 连屎都擦不干净
I got clipped in the arm. Can't even wipe my arse properly.
就我自己是没办法在你给的期限前做出来的
'On my own I won't make your deadline.'
有人能帮你做吗
Well, is there anyone that can help you?
没有信得过的
'No-one I trust.'
你信得过我吗
Would you trust me?
好了 到此为止
OK! Stop!
别再整了
No more!
你不会杀他吗
You won't kill him?
可以保证吗
Is that a guarantee?
-千真万确  -他在哪 拉里
- Cast iron. - Where is he, Larry?
诺曼在哪
Where's Norman?
布达佩斯
Budapest.
Budapest?
-地址呢  -我只去过那一次
- What's the address? - I was only there the once.
他当时来机场接我
He picked me up at the airport.
去他那花了多长时间
How long did it take to get from the airport to his place?
不知道 一小时左右吧
I don't know, about an hour?
-出了镇了  -是在村里吗
- It was out of town. - Was it a village?
还是郊区 那个地方什么样子
A suburb? What'd it look like?
在他那条街的转角处 有家咖啡店
There, there was a coffee shop at the corner of Norman's street.
后面还有马厩 里面有马
And there were stables out the back. With horses.
他住什么地方
What sort of place has he got?
房子 还是公寓
A house, apartment?
不是房子 是白色的大型建筑
It not a house, it's a big white building.
有大门和院子 我知道的就这些 我发誓
With a gate. And a yard. That's all I know. I swear.
我就知道这些
That is all I know!
你怎么找到我家的
How'd you find out where I live?
诺曼说的
Norman told me.
诺曼怎么知道的
How did Norman know?
诺曼和我的圈子不同
Norman moves in different circles than me.
他总有办法知道
He can find stuff out.
枪管 消音器 扳机
你好 我是努丽娅
'Hi. It's Nuria.'
通知
'A call'
所有搭乘EST119航班 前往布达佩斯 还未登机的旅客
'for all remaining passengers on flight EST119 flying to Budapest.'
请尽快前往五号登机口
'Please, proceed immediately to gate five'
并准备好您的登机牌
'and have your boarding passes ready.'
所以 这里有人是内鬼
So, one of these guys is a dirty little mole...
对 等我一分钟
Yep. Just, give me a minute.
我有亚历山大·杜根的消息
I have an update on Alexander Duggan.
是吗
Uh-huh?
他是个单身汉 注重细节 狙击好手
He was a loner. Details freak. Pure sniper material.
他所在的小队专门消灭塔利班领导人
His unit specialised in eliminating Taliban leaders.
杀了很多人
Killed a lot of people.
但他们2013年在赫尔曼德 被简易爆炸装置全灭
But they were taken out by an IED in Helmand in 2013.
这么说 杜根死了
So, Duggan is dead?
是的
Yep.
找到尸体了吗
Was his body recovered?
应该是找到了 但我再查一下吧
Well, I assume so, but I can check.
去吧
Yep.
好了
OK...
办公室的气氛有点诡异
Hey, bit of a weird atmosphere in the office.
猜疑越来越多
Paranoia levels are going through
你能顺便找一张杜根的照片吗
Can you get a photograph of Duggan while you're at it.
-行  -很好
- Yeah, copy that. - Great.
我扩大到机场90分钟车程范围
I've widened the parameters to make it a 90-minute radius from the airport.
他描述的是有大门和院子的巨大白色建筑
He described it as a big, white building with a gate and a yard.
街角有咖啡店 后面有马厩
Coffee shop on the corner of the street, stables at the back.
多久才能得到精确位置
How long until we have a precise location?
信息有点模糊
It's a little vague.
可能还得一会
Might take a while.
那就抓紧点 杀手又要行动了
Well, get a move on. An assassin's on the run.
好的 别催了
Right. No pressure then
你们给的信息太少了
You haven't given me much to work with.
思考者还是臭皮匠
'The Thinker or the Stinker?'
见鬼
Shit.
思考者还是臭皮匠
乌达查与他的资流软件引发争议
罗丹就是乌达查 豺狼的下一个目标
Rodan is UDC. The Jackal's next target.
风险无疑提高了
Well, that certainly raises the stakes.
他惹毛了一众大人物
He's been pissing off a lot of powerful people.
我猜你也告诉伊莎贝尔了吧
I assume you've shared this with Isabel?
你说过要尽量保密
You said keep the circle tight.
他知道 我们是老交情了
He knows. We go way back.
好吧 你下一步计划是什么
Alright. What's your next step?
我得找到诺曼·斯托克
I need to find Norman Stoke
我们大概知道诺曼在哪了
and we think we have a rough idea of where Norman is.
哪里
Where?
懂了
I get it.
但我推测 一旦你得到了确切地址
But I'm assuming as soon as you have a precise location,
你就想尽快出动 把他缉拿归案是吧
you'll want to move quickly and pick him up?
是的 就是这么计划的
Yeah, that's the plan.
这样一来 你就需要授权和后勤支援
For which you'll need authorisation and logistical support.
除了伊莎贝尔 唯一可以暗中提供这些帮助的 就只有我了
Apart from Isabel the only person who can do that, under the radar, is me.
如果要我的援助
If I'm to help,
我就得知道具体信息 他在哪
I need the details. Where is he?
布达佩斯附近
Somewhere near Budapest.
我们还不知道确切地址 但知道后会马上行动
We don't know where exactly, but as soon as we do we can move.
到时候我来安排
I'll start making arrangements.
准备好就告诉我
When you're ready to roll, let me know.
布达佩斯  匈牙利
喂 真及时
Yeah, in your own time.
我都站在这 等了二十分钟了
Been standing here for the past 20 minutes.
我知道
'I know.'
你比我想象中高
'You're taller than I imagined.'
-也更瘦  -行吧 你他妈在哪
- 'And slimmer.' - 'OK, where the fuck are you?'
去广场的东南角
Go to the south-east corner of the square.
我会接你
'I'll pick you up.'
有什么进展
What's the update?
我们找到了十七个可疑地点
'We've got seventeen possible locations'
-都距离机场不足九十分钟车程  -这样不行
- 'within 90 minutes of the airport.' - Yeah, that's not gonna work.
-缩小到六十分钟  -六十分钟车程范围内
- Take it down to sixty. - 'A 60-minute radius gives you...'
有十一个符合条件的
'..eleven locations that fit your criteria.'
啊 还是太多了
Ah, still too many.
你还有别的筛选条件吗
'Do you have anything else to narrow it down?'
没了
Nope.
好吧 我们再看看有没有别的办法
'Alright, we'll see what else we can come up with.'
祈求好运吧
Fingers crossed, hey.
下个路口左转就到他们家了
Their house is the next left.
嗨 安吉拉
Hi, Angela
-知道你带来了多大的破坏吗  -哇
- D'you have any idea how much damage you're causing? - Wow.
话这么直 我只是有话想和我丈夫还有孩子说
Straight in. I'm just here to talk to my husband and my child.
你能叫一下他们嘛
Can you call them, please
-你要真是好母亲 就不会出现在这  -好母亲  -差不多得了
- A good mother wouldn't have to be here. - A good mother? - That's enough.
-你不会想让我评论你的  -我不想
- You do NOT want me to comment on you -I do NOT want...
安吉拉 进去 我来处理
Angela, go inside. I'll deal with this.
没人想跟你说话
No-one's trying to speak to you.
-我想跟我丈夫和孩子说  -求你了 进去吧
- I'm trying to talk to my husband and my child. - Please, just go back inside...
你说 我来处理
'I'll deal with this.'
-真的假的 拜托  -从她的角度想一下吧
- Really?! Please. - Think of it from her point of view.
我为什么要从她的角度考虑
Why do I need to look at it from her point of view...
我来这想跟你和孩子说话 她一直叨叨
...when I'm here to speak to you and my child and she's chatting-
发生的这些对你来说也许寻常 但对我们来说
What happened might be normal to you, but for us,
-真的很他妈吓人  -好 贾斯敏在吗
- it's really fucking scary! - OK. Jasmine, is she there?
发生什么了
What's going on?
她很好 和男孩们在一块 他们对她真的很好
She's fine, she's with the boys. They've been really great with her.
安吉拉也是
So has Angela.
你要回家吗
Are you coming home?
还是说 你要住在你该死的前妻家
Or are you staying here with your fucking ex-wife?
-嗯  -好吧
- Hm? - OK.
一开始 你就对我很坦诚
From the start, you've been really upfront with me
说你多爱你的工作 对你多么重要
about how much you love your job and how important it is to you, OK?
但昨晚你把危险带回了我们的家
But last night you brought danger into our home.
刀架在我女儿脖子上
And between that knife being held at my daughters neck
你还举枪对着她
and that gun you had pointed in her direction,
贾斯敏差点就没命了
Jasmine could've been fucking killed.
-但她没有 我解决了  -她说你折磨那个男人
- But she wasn't. I dealt with it. - She said you tortured the man.
他有我需要的信息
He had information and I needed to get it from him.
我完全不想知道
I don't, I don't even wanna know
你这句话的意思 但是
what you're saying with that statement, but...
不管怎么说 这实在
...either way, Jesus Christ, it's...
不像一个好母亲会做的 比安卡
It's not really ideal mothering is it, Bianca?
我努力做一个好母亲 保罗 但我要工作
I am trying, Paul, but I have a job to do-
我们谁不工作啊
We've all got jobs to do!
只是我们这样的人知道 为了家庭
It's just that some of us understand that in family,
你就是得做出妥协
you've gotta make compromises.
你在大学工作 你可以开会迟到一下
In your job, you can be late for a conference or
材料晚交一会儿
bring in a paper late
但我的工作 不能这样
and it's just... My job,
如果我没在指定时间
if I'm not where they tell me to be,
出现在准确地点
at the exact time that they tell me to be there,
就会有人丧命
then someone dies.
懂吗
Do you understand?!
你真的变了
I don't recognise you anymore.
欢迎光临寒舍
Welcome to my humble abode.
你说的七十五米 是吧
Seventy-five metres, you said?
是的
Yeah.
-有什么限制吗  -是这样
- What are the limitations? - Right. So,
主要限制是大小
main limitation's gonna be size,
枪机和枪栓的体积别超过这么大
so the action and bolt should be no bulkier than about that.
-需要扳机护环吗  -不用 但我想问
- D'you need a trigger guard? - No, but I was wondering
我能不能像上次一样 有可拆卸的板机
if I could get the trigger removable like the last one,
这样我就可以在开火前装好
so that I can attach it just before firing.
-为什么  -因为整体结构需要与这个匹配
- Why? - Ah, because the whole mechanism needs to fit into that.
这样啊
Oh, yes.
-不错 非常聪明  -谢谢
- That's nice. That's very clever. - Thank you.
我还提到过 有扫描仪
And I mentioned the scanner.
估计非常灵敏
And I think that's gonna be pretty sensitive.
骨折靴由塑料和聚合物制成
Ah, fracture boots are made of plastic and polymer.
可以轻松通过扫描仪
They'll get through the scanner easy,
但击发机构 还有枪管
but the... the firing mechanism and... the barrel,
会被扫描仪发现
they're gonna show up.
能不能全都用塑料做
So, I was wondering about the whole thing plastic?
你不能用塑料做枪管
Y-You can't make a barrel out of plastic.
机械加工 3D打印都做不到
Doesn't matter if it's machined or 3D printed,
不过 我们可以试试
but we could try
用轻质合金做一个低射弹量的一次性枪管
a low-round-count disposable barrel made from a lightweight alloy.
那能开几枪
Right, and how many rounds would that get me?
通常来说
Usually it'll be a...
只能开一枪 但是有我这样的大师在
...one-shot throwaway, but with a maestro like me,
可以开八枪
you can get up to eight shots.
至少七枪
Seven, for sure.
好 足够了
Alright, no, that'll be plenty.
能再装一个消音器吗
Er, can I get a silencer as well?
我们可以把消音器的核心打印出来
We could print the suppressor core.
能混过安检
It would confuse the... scanner operators.
时间够吗
What we thinking time wise?
得花上四五个小时写程序
Ah, it's gonna takes us four or five hours to write the programme
还要十个小时打印
and then... another ten hours to print.
你时间充裕吗
Do you have time for that?
-如果现在开始就够  -好的
If we start now, yeah. Alright, well...
我要去拉个屎 冲个澡 抽根烟
I'm off for a shite, a shower, and a smoke.
然后就可以开始了
Then I'll be ready.
要是查尔斯知道我们进来过 就麻烦了
你能复原吗
可以 别担心
但是 努丽娅
你要是根本不相信他 干嘛要复原
阿尔瓦罗 你把它复原就行
听我的 好吗
你说了算
二号摄像头 实时画面
好了
Right.
我们可以开始了吗
Shall we get started?
开始吧
Let us.
G9
G, nine...
M82
...M, eight, two.
继续
Yeah.
M104
M, one, four, zero.
继续
Yeah.
S14
S, one, four.
打印开始了 需要十到十二个小时
That's the printing started. It'll take ten, twelve hours.
我的止痛药
Pain medication.
是啊
Yeah, yeah
你要来点吗
You have a wee drop?
-不了 谢谢  -你会改主意的
- No, I'm good thank you. - Ah, you might change your mind.
好了
There we go.
干杯
Cheers.
那我喝点吧 干杯
Go on then. Well done.
老天 看看这些瓶瓶罐罐
Jesus, look at these glasses.
这地方真需要女人打理一下
This place could do with a woman's touch.
你有过老婆吗
Did you ever have a wife?
老婆
A wife?
对
Yeah.
没有
Nah.
好吧 差点娶了一个
Well, once... nearly.
她是个好女人 厨艺一流
She was a great woman, great cook,
床上功夫了得
great in bed...
她是个很好的伴侣
She was great company.
但是我们这种人
Ah, but sure in... our game...
不能有妻子
...you can't have a wife.
你这样觉得
You think?
当然
A hundred percent.
特别是被爱情冲昏头脑时
Especially if you fall in love with them.
而我总被爱情冲昏头脑
And I was always falling in love.
真是个噩梦 我是个无可救药的浪漫主义者
Fucking nightmare. I'm a hopeless romantic.
你是因为爱情出国的吗
Is that what that trip abroad was? Was that a romantic thing?
不不不 那是生意
No, no. No. That was... That was business.
有个客户有特殊需求 像你一样
A client with specialist needs, like you.
你去了哪
Where'd you go?
机密
Client confidentiality.
你去了哪
Where'd you go?
这沉默让我
The silence makes me...
有点紧张
...a bit nervous.
白俄罗斯 行了吧 这下安心了吗
It was Belarus... alright? Does that settle your nerves?
诺曼 谁在白俄罗斯找上你 俄罗斯人吗
Who came calling for you in Belarus, Norman? Russians?
他们是英国口音
They had English accents.
你看到他们了吗
D'you see them?
-那个开枪打我的贱女人 我看到她了  -女的啊
- The bitch who shot me, I saw her alright, aye - A woman?
黑人女性 用的是格洛克17手枪
Black woman. She had a Glock 17.
一个持枪的英国黑人女性
A black... armed British woman...
在白俄罗斯
...in Belarus.
你骗我 老头
You lied to me, old man.
我怎么骗你了
Wh... How am I lying to you?
我实话实说
I'm telling you all about it, aren't I-
你怎么逃脱军情六处抓捕的 诺曼
How did you get away from an MI6 snatch squad, Norman?
我得到了一点帮助
I had a bit of help.
这样啊
Yeah.
我收到了密报 说他们要来
I got a tip-off they were on their way.
谁告诉你的
Who from?
不知道
I don't know.
没有电话号码
There was no number...
只有一条短信 写着快撤离
It was... it was just a message said, 'Clear out now.'
朋友 你是位艺术家
You're an artist, my friend,
你总是行事小心
and you've always been discreet.
但要是你一时大意...
But if that changes...
文森特
什么事
Yeah?
有个好消息 我们可能找到了诺曼的位置
'I've got good news. We think we found Norman's location.'
一个在洛林奇的废弃工厂 符合所有特征
'It fits all the parameters, an abandoned factory in a place called Lorinci.'
你确定吗
Are you sure?
确定
'As sure as we can be.'
大型白色建筑 距离布达佩斯机场56分钟车程
'Large white building, 56 minutes from Budapest airport.'
这是最接近的了
'Right now it's our best shot.'
欧斯 我们可能找到了
Osi, we might have a location.
我们有授权吗
Do we have authorisation?
就在布达佩斯吗
'So, it is Budapest?'
-对 就在布达佩斯  -我会通知匈牙利人
Yeah, it's Budapest. 'I'll inform the Hungarians'
我们会在他们的地盘上行动
'that we're going to be operating on their turf.'
你赶去机场 我去请求授权
'You get to the airport, I'll get the authorisation.'
如果还需要什么 给我电话
'If you need anything else, give me a call.'
你相信他吗
Do you trust him?
你呢
Do you?
试试看
Try it on.
这个穿着
Yeah that's...
竟然挺舒服的
...weirdly comfortable.
安检会探测到金属部件
The scanner will pick up the metal components,
但安检员应该不会觉得意外
but that shouldn't surprise the operator.
如果他让你脱下来
If he asks you to take it off,
你可以用医疗借口让他滚
you can tell him to fuck off on medical grounds.
教我怎么组装
Show me how to build it.
这简直就是件艺术品
That is a fucking work of art, that is.
附近哪里可以不引人注意
So, where's the nearest place I can take this for a spin
-试试枪  -路尽头右转
- without attracting attention? - Oh, top of the road, turn right.
火车轨道那儿左转 然后直走
Left at the train tracks and keep going
-直到看见森林  -好的
- until you get to some woods. - Right.
你可以开我的车去
You can take my car.
我要去睡觉了
I'm off to bed.
这些你应该用得上
You'll need these.
里面有些特殊子弹
Couple of special ones in there, too.
切记
Remember...
不是炮铜子弹
It's not gunmetal.
你可以开八枪
You'll get eight shots from it.
稳妥起见 尽量少试几枪
To be on the safe side, keep the test firing to a minimum.
欢迎来到布达佩斯 当地时间为
'Welcome to Budapest. The local time is...'
1点35分 祝您一路顺风
'..01:35. We'd like to wish you a safe onward journey.'
他在那
There he is.
杂货店
五金店
很抱歉 但是
Actually sorry, d'you know what,
我想要那个小的
can I get the small one?
-多少钱  -两千福林
- How much is that? - Two thousand, please.
给你 非常感谢
Two thousand, thank you very much.
44分钟后接近目标　距离目标51.0英里
你好
Hi...
陌生人
'..stranger.'
你好 亲爱的
Hello, my love.
你还好吗
Are you alright?
是的
Yes.
真的吗
'Are you sure?'
我一直给你打电话
'I've been trying you.'
你确定你没事吗
'You sure you're OK?'
我很好
'I'm fine.'
-只是需要一些时间思考  -好的
- 'I just...needed some time to think.' - OK.
-希望一切都安好  -我也希望
- Well, all good I'm hoping? - 'Yeah, I think so.'
-你什么时候回来  -四五天吧 最多一周
- 'When are you coming back?' - Four or five days. A week at most.
我保证 我这次回来 就赖着不走了
And then I promise you, you are gonna be so bored of me,
你求着我走都来不及
you're gonna be begging me to leave.
我只是想让一切回到原来的样子
I just want everything to be the way it used to be.
就在这条路左侧
It's just up here on the left.
-我们的儿子怎么样了  -他很好
- How's our little boy doing? - 'He's great.'
-很闹腾 但很好  -我好想你们俩
- 'Exhausting, but great.' - I miss you both so much.
我们俩也想你
'We miss you, too.'
但是我们需要认真讨论一些事情 查尔斯
'But there's something we need to discuss, Charles.'
-听见我说话了吗  -是的
'Did you hear me?' Yeah...
非常符合拉里的描述
Certainly fits Larry's description.
这很重要 查尔斯
This is important, Charles.
我得挂了 晚点回你好吗 爱你
I've gotta run now, but I'll speak to you in a sec, OK? Love you.
-再见  -再见
- 'Bye.' - Bye, bye.
他还在骗我 阿尔瓦罗
我敢肯定
谢谢
随时可以断电
We can cut the power,
都安排好了
it's all arranged.
我不希望白俄罗斯的事重演
I just don't want a repeat of Belarus.
你想做什么
What d'you wanna do?
都听你号令
It's your call.
断电
记得活捉他 听到没
Right. Remember we need him alive, yeah? OK...
什么事
'Yeah?'
你有不少访客 其中一个
You've got visitors. One of them
看起来像你军情六处的朋友 清理完后快跑
'looks like your friend from MI6. Clean up and get out now.'
一定要清理干净
Just make sure you clean up.
操
Fuck...
Fuck.
删除文件
不要这个
OK. Not this one.
来吧 你们这些混蛋
Come on, you bastards!
破门
Breaching!
前进
Move!
去死吧
Fuck off!
前进
Move!
操
Fuck.
你好啊 诺曼
Hello, Norman.
我知道 有人用你造的枪杀了曼弗雷德·费斯特
I know you made the gun that killed Manfred Fest.
-你知道个屁  -你在这里
You know fuck all. And here you are...
又做了一支新的 诺曼
...making a new one already, Norman.
这支也是给豺狼的吗
Is this for the Jackal as well?
我他妈完全不知道你在说什么
I haven't the foggiest idea what you're talking about.
一只胳膊可造不出枪吧
Must be impossible with just the one arm?
哦 这些是什么
Oh, what's all this?
有朋友来拜访你吗 诺曼
Did you have a little friend over, Norman?
那就解释得通了
Well, that makes sense.
你一个人一定又无助又凄惨
You're a pretty sad specimen on your own, eh?
操你妈
Fuck you.
告诉我们豺狼是谁
Tell us who the Jackal is.
我他妈完全不知道你们在说什么
I haven't the foggiest idea what you're talking about.
得了吧 诺曼
Ah, come on Norman...
豺狼的真名是什么
What's the Jackal's name?
我他妈完全不知道你在说什么
I haven't the foggiest idea what you're talking about.
我觉得你知道 诺曼
Oh, I think you do, Norman.
我们知道豺狼又接了一个暗杀任务
We know the Jackal's been contracted for another hit.
不难想象 他需要重新定制武器
Makes sense he'd need another bespoke weapon.
鉴于你上一支枪做得那么好
And after you did such a good job with the last one.
换做是我
Well, if it was me,
如果他这次不找我做 我还会有点难过呢
I'd be hurt if he didn't ask me for the next one.
这是他的东西
This is his. This... This is HIS.
对吧 诺曼
Isn't it, Norman?
嗯
Eh?
豺狼在附近 对吧
The Jackal's here, isn't he?
-走吧 我们把他拖进车里  -不
- Come on. Let's get him in the car. - No.
等等
Wait.
豺狼来过这里 他的东西在这儿
The Jackal's been here. His things are here...
他会回来的
...so he'll be back.
让丽娜和塔马斯盯紧街上的情况
Tell Lina and Tamas to keep watch on the street.
计划有变 丽娜留在车附近
Change of plan. Lina, stay by the car.
-塔马斯 继续监视  -收到
- Tamas, take your position. - 'Copy.'
我们会在这等 诺曼
Well, while we're waiting, Norman,
告诉我你是怎么知道我家庭住址的
you can tell me how you got my home address.
嗯
Hm?
是白俄罗斯那次的泄密者告诉你的吗
Was it the same person that tipped you off that we were in Belarus?
我他妈完全不知道你在说什么
I haven't the foggiest idea what you're talking about.
你就不好奇是谁泄露了你的位置吗
Aren't you wondering who tipped us off about you?
拉里泄露的
It was Larry.
没错
Yeah, that's right.
一定很难接受吧
Man, it must be really hard,
发现你哥出卖了你
finding out that it was your own brother who sold you out.
更难接受的是
And it must be even harder,
你面前的这个人
when the person standing in front of you
撬开了你哥的嘴 也会把你们俩一起
is the one who made him talk, and is gonna put you both
送进监狱 度过余生
in jail for the rest of your fucking lives.
有枪手 左侧包抄
Shooter. Flanking left.
有人看见他吗 能看见他吗
'Does anyone have eyes on? Can you see him?!'
-不能  -不能
'Negative.' 'Negative.'
我看见了 他在马厩旁边
'I have eyes on. He's by the stables.'
收到 盯住
'Copy that. Eyes on.'
目标移动中 骑着一匹马
He's going mobile... on a fucking horse.
追上去
'In pursuit.'
丽娜 接我上车
'Lina, pick me up.'
约翰·韦恩是以出演西部片而闻名的美国男演员
你也没说我们的目标是约翰·韦恩啊
'You didn't tell me you were after John-fucking-Wayne.'
快
Go, go, go!
-你没事吧  -没事
You OK? Yes.
射中防弹背心了
He hit the vest.
操
Fuck!
FUCK!
操